Guide to the Rights and Wrongs Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Rights and Wrongs records
1990-1996
1993-1996
MS 1821
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
161.75
(177 boxes)
The records consist of videotapes, topical files, and other materials from the production, Rights and Wrongs, a weekly news magazine that ran from 1993 to 1996 and concerned global human rights issues.
Globalvision, Inc
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from The International Center for Global Communications Foundation by the Yale University Library and transferred to Manuscripts and Archives, 2003.
Conditions Governing Access
Series I to III are unprocessed and may contain sensitive information or be in a physical state that would prohibit use. Researchers wishing to request access should email mssa.assist@yale.edu requesting specific box numbers in order to initiate the review process, which may take several weeks.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of videotapes, topical files, and other materials from the production, Rights and Wrongs, a weekly news magazine that ran from 1993 to 1996 and concerned global human rights issues.
Series IV, Programs, consists of the programs as aired.
Arrangement
Arranged in four series: Series I. Camera Originals, 1993-1996; Series II. Stock Footage, 1993-1996; Series III. Paper Files, 1993-1996; Series IV. Programs, 1993-1996.
Biographical / Historical
Rights and Wrongs was a weekly television news magazine that ran from 1993 to 1996 and concerned global human rights issues. The program was hosted by Charlayne Hunter-Gault and was broadcast on 85 public television stations and in 35 foreign countries.
Human rights
- Camera Originals, Circa 1990-1996; Series I
  Arrangement
  The series is arranged by creator assigned tape number.
  Scope and Contents
  The series consists of original videotapes.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
  The material is unprocessed and may contain sensitive information or be in a physical state that would prohibit use. Researchers wishing to request access should email mssa.assist@yale.edu requesting specific box numbers in order to initiate the review process, which may take several weeks.
  - RT93 1000: Michael Posner #1, 1990 January 3; 1 (Box RT93 1000)
  - RT93 1001: Jeri Laber Interview Tape 1, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1001)
  - RT93 1002: Sidney Jone #2, 1992 November 1; 1 (Box RT93 1002)
  - RT93 1003, 1990 January 8; 1 (Box RT93 1003)
  - RT93 1004, 1990 January 8; 1 (Box RT93 1004)
  - RT93 1005, 1991 January 30; 1 (Box RT93 1005)
  - RT93 1006, 1991 January 30; 1 (Box RT93 1006)
  - RT93 1007, 1991 January 24; 1 (Box RT93 1007)
  - RT93 1008, 1991 January 24; 1 (Box RT93 1008)
  - RT93 1009, 1991 January 14; 1 (Box RT93 1009)
  - RT93 1010, 1991 January 14; 1 (Box RT93 1010)
  - RT93 1011, 1991 January 9; 1 (Box RT93 1011)
  - RT93 1012, 1991 January 14; 1 (Box RT93 1012)
  - RT93 1013, 1990 January 8; 1 (Box RT93 1013)
  - RT93 1014, 1991 January 30; 1 (Box RT93 1014)
  - RT93 1015, 1990 January 8; 1 (Box RT93 1015)
  - RT93 1016, 1991 January 15; 1 (Box RT93 1016)
  - RT93 1017, 1991 January 15; 1 (Box RT93 1017)
  - RT93 1018, 1991 March 10; 1 (Box RT93 1018)
  - RT93 1019, 1991 March 10; 1 (Box RT93 1019)
  - RT93 1020, 1991 October 3; 1 (Box RT93 1020)
  - RT93 1022, 1991 March 10; 1 (Box RT93 1022)
  - RT93 1023, 1991 February 1; 1 (Box RT93 1023)
  - RT93 1024, 1991 February 1; 1 (Box RT93 1024)
  - RT93 1025, 1991 February 1; 1 (Box RT93 1025)
  - RT93 1026, 1990 January 8; 1 (Box RT93 1026)
  - RT93 1027, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1027)
  - RT93 1028, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1028)
  - RT93 1029, 1991 December 18; 1 (Box RT93 1029)
  - RT93 1030, 1991 December 18; 1 (Box RT93 1030)
  - RT93 1031, 1990 January 3; 1 (Box RT93 1031)
  - RT93 1032, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1032)
  - RT93 1033, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1033)
  - RT93 1034, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1034)
  - RT93 1035, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1035)
  - RT93 1036, 1991 July 29; 1 (Box RT93 1036)
  - RT93 1037, 1991 February 1; 1 (Box RT93 1037)
  - RT93 1038, 1991 February 1; 1 (Box RT93 1038)
  - RT93 1039, 1989 March 1; 1 (Box RT93 1039)
  - RT93 1040, 1991 January 15; 1 (Box RT93 1040)
  - RT93 1041, 1991 January 15; 1 (Box RT93 1041)
  - RT93 1042, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1042)
  - RT93 1043, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1043)
  - RT93 1044, 1991 January 30; 1 (Box RT93 1044)
  - RT93 1045, 1991 January 30; 1 (Box RT93 1045)
  - RT93 1046, 1990 December 18; 1 (Box RT93 1046)
  - RT93 1047, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1047)
  - RT93 1048, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1048)
  - RT93 1049, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1049)
  - RT93 1050, 1991 January 24; 1 (Box RT93 1050)
  - RT93 1051, 1991 February 1; 1 (Box RT93 1051)
  - RT93 1052, 1990 January 8; 1 (Box RT93 1052)
  - RT93 1053, 1991 January 8; 1 (Box RT93 1053)
  - RT93 1054, 1991 January 8; 1 (Box RT93 1054)
  - RT93 1055, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1055)
  - RT93 1056, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1056)
  - RT93 1057, 1992 June 30; 1 (Box RT93 1057)
  - RT93 1058, 1992 June 30; 1 (Box RT93 1058)
  - RT93 1059, 1991 January 8; 1 (Box RT93 1059)
  - RT93 1060, 1992 April 1; 1 (Box RT93 1060)
  - RT93 1061, 1992 April 1; 1 (Box RT93 1061)
  - RT93 1062, 1992 March 23 (Box 4)
  - RT93 1063, 1992 March 23 (Box 4)
  - RT93 1064, 1992 March 23 (Box 4)
  - RT93 1065, 1992 August 18; 1 (Box RT93 1065)
  - RT93 1066, 1992 August 18; 1 (Box RT93 1066)
  - RT93 1067, 1992 July 1; 1 (Box RT93 1067)
  - RT93 1068, 1992 December 10; 1 (Box RT93 1068)
  - RT93 1069, 1992 December 10; 1 (Box RT93 1069)
  - RT93 1070, 1992 December 10; 1 (Box RT93 1070)
  - RT93 1071, 1992 December 10; 1 (Box RT93 1071)
  - RT93 1072, 1992 December 10; 1 (Box RT93 1072)
  - RT93 1073, 1992 December 10; 1 (Box RT93 1073)
  - RT93 1074, 1992 December 10; 1 (Box RT93 1074)
  - RT93 1075, 1992 December 10; 1 (Box RT93 1075)
  - RT93 1076, 1992 December 10; 1 (Box RT93 1076)
  - RT93 1077, 1992 December 3; 1 (Box RT93 1077)
  - RT93 1078, 1992 December 3; 1 (Box RT93 1078)
  - RT93 1079, 1992 February 29; 1 (Box RT93 1079)
  - RT93 1080, 1992 February 29; 1 (Box RT93 1080)
  - RT93 1081, 1992 February 29; 1 (Box RT93 1081)
  - RT93 1082, 1992 November 10; 1 (Box RT93 1082)
  - RT93 1083, 1992 October 6; 1 (Box RT93 1083)
  - RT93 1084, 1992 October 6; 1 (Box RT93 1084)
  - RT93 1085, 1992 October 6; 1 (Box RT93 1085)
  - RT93 1086: Earth Parliament Interviews Danny Schecter with Noel Brown and indigenous people, 1992 August 8; 1 (Box RT93 1086)
  - RT93 1087: Interview with Asma Abdel Halim, 1993 February 19; 1 (Box RT93 1087)
  - RT93 1088: Interview with Asma Abdel Halim and an interview with Ylarra Suarez, 1993 February 19; 1 (Box RT93 1088)
  - RT93 1089: Interview with Maria Suarez, 1993 February 19; 1 (Box RT93 1089)
  - RT93 1090: Interview with Maria Suarez, 1993 February 19; 1 (Box RT93 1090)
  - RT93 1091: Hearings and interview of men from the Philippines, 1993 February 19; 1 (Box RT93 1091)
  - RT93 1092: RT 168 interview, 1993 February 19; 1 (Box RT93 1092)
  - RT93 1093: RT 169, 1993 February 19; 1 (Box RT93 1093)
  - RT93 1094: RT 170, 1993 February 19; 1 (Box RT93 1094)
  - RT93 1095, 1992 March 23; 1 (Box RT93 1095)
  - RT93 1096, 1992 March 23; 1 (Box RT93 1096)
  - RT93 1097, 1992 March 23; 1 (Box RT93 1097)
  - RT93 1098, 1992 August 18; 1 (Box RT93 1098)
  - RT93 1099, 1992 October 1; 1 (Box RT93 1099)
  - RT93 1100, 1992 October 1; 1 (Box RT93 1100)
  - RT93 1101, 1992 October 1; 1 (Box RT93 1101)
  - RT93 1102, 1993 March 2; 1 (Box RT93 1102)
  - RT93 1103, 1993 March 1; 1 (Box RT93 1103)
  - RT93 1104, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1104)
  - RT93 1105, 1993 Masr 1; 1 (Box RT93 1105)
  - RT93 1106, 1993 March 1; 1 (Box RT93 1106)
  - RT93 1107, 1993 March 2; 1 (Box RT93 1107)
  - RT93 1108, 1993 March 2; 1 (Box RT93 1108)
  - RT93 1109: Dalai Lama at Forum, 1992 June 1; 1 (Box RT93 1109)
  - RT93 1110, 1992 June 1; 1 (Box RT93 1110)
  - RT93 1111, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1111)
  - RT93 1112, 1992 November 1; 1 (Box RT93 1112)
  - RT93 1113, 1993 March 4; 1 (Box RT93 1113)
  - RT93 1114, 1993 March 4; 1 (Box RT93 1114)
  - RT93 1115 [has VHS use copy], 1993 March 4; 1 (Box RT93 1115)
  - RT93 1116 [has VHS use copy], 1993 March 4; 1 (Box RT93 1116)
  - RT93 1117, 1993 March 8; 1 (Box RT93 1117)
  - RT93 1118, 1993 March 8; 1 (Box RT93 1118)
  - RT93 1119, 1993 March 8; 1 (Box RT93 1119)
  - RT93 1120, 1993 March 9; 1 (Box RT93 1120)
  - RT93 1121, 1993 March 9; 1 (Box RT93 1121)
  - RT93 1122, 1993 March 10; 1 (Box RT93 1122)
  - RT93 1123, 1993 March 10; 1 (Box RT93 1123)
  - RT93 1124, 1993 March 10; 1 (Box RT93 1124)
  - RT93 1125, 1993 March 10; 1 (Box RT93 1125)
  - RT93 1126, 1993 March 10; 1 (Box RT93 1126)
  - RT93 1127, 1993 March 11; 1 (Box RT93 1127)
  - RT93 1128: Tape 125, 1991 March 12; 1 (Box RT93 1128)
  - RT93 1129: Tape 130, 1991 March 12; 1 (Box RT93 1129)
  - RT93 1130: Tape 136, 1991 March 13; 1 (Box RT93 1130)
  - RT93 1132, 1993 March 12; 1 (Box RT93 1132)
  - RT93 1133, 1993 March 12; 1 (Box RT93 1133)
  - RT93 1134, 1993 March 12; 1 (Box RT93 1134)
  - RT93 1135, 1993 March 12; 1 (Box RT93 1135)
  - RT93 1136, 1993 March 12; 1 (Box RT93 1136)
  - RT93 1137, 1993 March 12; 1 (Box RT93 1137)
  - RT93 1138, 1993 March 12; 1 (Box RT93 1138)
  - RT93 1139, 1993 March 12; 1 (Box RT93 1139)
  - RT93 1140, 1993 March 12; 1 (Box RT93 1140)
  - RT93 1141, 1993 March 12; 1 (Box RT93 1141)
  - RT93 1142, 1993 March 15; 1 (Box RT93 1142)
  - RT93 1143, 1993 March 15; 1 (Box RT93 1143)
  - RT93 1144, 1993 March 15; 1 (Box RT93 1144)
  - RT93 1145, 1993 March 15; 1 (Box RT93 1145)
  - RT93 1146, 1993 March 12; 1 (Box RT93 1146)
  - RT93 1147, 1993 March 15; 1 (Box RT93 1147)
  - RT93 1148, 1993 March 15; 1 (Box RT93 1148)
  - RT93 1149, 1993 March 15; 1 (Box RT93 1149)
  - RT93 1150, 1993 March 15; 1 (Box RT93 1150)
  - RT93 1151, 1993 March 16; 1 (Box RT93 1151)
  - RT93 1152, 1993 March 16; 1 (Box RT93 1152)
  - RT93 1153, 1993 March 16; 1 (Box RT93 1153)
  - RT93 1154, 1993 March 17; 1 (Box RT93 1154)
  - RT93 1155, 1993 March 17; 1 (Box RT93 1155)
  - RT93 1156, 1993 March 17; 1 (Box RT93 1156)
  - RT93 1157, 1993 March 17; 1 (Box RT93 1157)
  - RT93 1158, 1993 March 16; 1 (Box RT93 1158)
  - RT93 1159, 1993 March 16; 1 (Box RT93 1159)
  - RT93 1160, 1993 March 17; 1 (Box RT93 1160)
  - RT93 1161, 1003 March 17; 1 (Box RT93 1161)
  - RT93 1162, 1993 March 18; 1 (Box RT93 1162)
  - RT93 1163, 1993 March 18; 1 (Box RT93 1163)
  - RT93 1164, 1993 March 18; 1 (Box RT93 1164)
  - RT93 1165, 1993 March 18; 1 (Box RT93 1165)
  - RT93 1166, 1993 March 19; 1 (Box RT93 1166)
  - RT93 1167, 1993 March 19; 1 (Box RT93 1167)
  - RT93 1168, 1993 March 19; 1 (Box RT93 1168)
  - RT93 1169, 1993 March 22; 1 (Box RT93 1169)
  - RT93 1170, 1993 March 22; 1 (Box RT93 1170)
  - RT93 1171, 1993 March 22; 1 (Box RT93 1171)
  - RT93 1172, 1993 March 23; 1 (Box RT93 1172)
  - RT93 1173, 1993 March 23; 1 (Box RT93 1173)
  - RT93 1174, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1174)
  - RT93 1175, 1993 March 17; 1 (Box RT93 1175)
  - RT93 1176, 1993 March 17; 1 (Box RT93 1176)
  - RT93 1179, Undated; 1 (Box RT93 1179)
  - RT93 1180, 1993 March 23; 1 (Box RT93 1180)
  - RT93 1181, 1993 March 23 (Box RT93_1181)
  - RT93 1182, 1993 March 23 (Box RT93_1182)
  - RT93 1184, 1993 March 24 (Box RT93_1184)
  - RT93 1185, 1993 March 24 (Box RT93_1185)
  - RT93 1186, 1993 March 24 (Box RT93_1186)
  - RT93 1187, 1993 March 24 (Box RT93_1187)
  - RT93 1188, 1993 March 24 (Box RT93_1188)
  - RT93 1189, 1993 March 24 (Box RT93_1189)
  - RT93 1190, 1993 March 24 (Box RT93_1190)
  - RT93 1191, 1993 March 24 (Box RT93_1191)
  - RT93 1192, 1993 March 15 (Box RT93_1192)
  - RT93 1193, 1993 March 15 (Box RT93_1193)
  - RT93 1195, 1993 March 23 (Box RT93_1195)
  - RT93 1196, 1993 March 25 (Box RT93_1196)
  - RT93 1197, 1993 March 25 (Box RT93_1197)
  - RT93 1198, 1993 March 25 (Box RT93_1198)
  - RT93 1199, 1993 March 30 (Box RT93_1199)
  - RT93 1200, 1993 March 30 (Box RT93_1200)
  - RT93 1201, 1993 March 30 (Box RT93_1201)
  - RT93 1202, 1993 March 30 (Box RT93_1202)
  - RT93 1203, 1993 March 30 (Box RT93_1203)
  - RT93 1204, 1993 March 31 (Box RT93_1204)
  - RT93 1205, 1993 March 31 (Box RT93_1205)
  - RT93 1206, 1993 March 31 (Box RT93_1206)
  - RT93 1207, 1993 March 31 (Box RT93_1207)
  - RT93 1208, 1993 March 27 (Box RT93_1208)
  - RT93 1209, 1993 March 27 (Box RT93_1209)
  - RT93 1210, 1993 April 4 (Box RT93_1210)
  - RT93 1211, 1993 April 4 (Box RT93_1211)
  - RT93 1212, 1993 April 4 (Box RT93_1212)
  - RT93 1213, 1993 April 6 (Box RT93_1213)
  - RT93 1214, 1993 April 5 (Box RT93_1214)
  - RT93 1215, 1993 April 5 (Box RT93_1215)
  - RT93 1216, 1993 April 6 (Box RT93_1216)
  - RT93 1217, 1993 April 6 (Box RT93_1217)
  - RT93 1218, 1993 April 6 (Box RT93_1218)
  - RT93 1219, 1993 April 6 (Box RT93_1219)
  - RT93 1220, 1993 April 6 (Box RT93_1220)
  - RT93 1221, 1993 April 5 (Box RT93_1221)
  - RT93 1222, Undated (Box RT93_1222)
  - RT93 1223, 1993 April 7 (Box RT93_1223)
  - RT93 1224, 1993 April 7 (Box RT93_1224)
  - RT93 1225, 1993 April 15 (Box RT93_1225)
  - RT93 1226, 1993 April 15 (Box RT93_1226)
  - RT93 1227, 1993 April 15 (Box RT93_1227)
  - RT93 1228, 1993 April 15 (Box RT93_1228)
  - RT93 1229, 1993 April 9 (Box RT93_1229)
  - RT93 1230, 1993 April 9 (Box RT93_1230)
  - RT93 1231, 1993 April 12 (Box RT93_1231)
  - RT93 1232, 1993 April 12 (Box RT93_1232)
  - RT93 1233, 1993 April 14 (Box RT93_1233)
  - RT93 1234, 1993 April 12 (Box RT93_1234)
  - RT93 1235, 1993 April 12 (Box RT93_1235)
  - RT93 1236, 1993 April 12 (Box RT93_1236)
  - RT93 1238, 1993 March 29 (Box RT93_1238)
  - RT93 1239, 1993 April 15 (Box RT93_1239)
  - RT93 1240, 1993 April 16 (Box RT93_1240)
  - RT93 1241, 1993 April 16 (Box RT93_1241)
  - RT93 1242, 1993 April 16 (Box RT93_1242)
  - RT93 1243, 1993 April 16 (Box RT93_1243)
  - RT93 1244, 1993 April 20 (Box RT93_1244)
  - RT93 1245, 1993 April 20 (Box RT93_1245)
  - RT93 1246, 1993 February 4 (Box RT93_1246)
  - RT93 1247, 1993 February 4 (Box RT93_1247)
  - RT93 1248, 1993 February 4 (Box RT93_1248)
  - RT93 1249, 1993 February 4 (Box RT93_1249)
  - RT93 1250, 1993 February 4 (Box RT93_1250)
  - RT93 1251, Undated (Box RT93_1251)
  - RT93 1252, 1993 April 20 (Box RT93_1252)
  - RT93 1253, 1993 April 21 (Box RT93_1253)
  - RT93 1254, 1993 April 21 (Box RT93_1254)
  - RT93 1257, 1993 April 19 (Box RT93_1257)
  - RT93 1258, 1993 April 19 (Box RT93_1258)
  - RT93 1259, 1993 April 12 (Box RT93_1259)
  - RT93 1260, 1993 April 12 (Box RT93_1260)
  - RT93 1261, 1993 April 21 (Box RT93_1261)
  - RT93 1262, 1993 April 21 (Box RT93_1262)
  - RT93 1263, 1993 April 21 (Box RT93_1263)
  - RT93 1264, 1993 April 21 (Box RT93_1264)
  - RT93 1265, 1993 April 6 (Box RT93_1265)
  - RT93 1266, 1993 April 6 (Box RT93_1266)
  - RT93 1268, 1993 April 5 (Box RT93_1268)
  - RT93 1270, 1993 April 6 (Box RT93_1270)
  - RT93 1271, 1993 April 23 (Box RT93_1271)
  - RT93 1272, 1993 April 23 (Box RT93_1272)
  - RT93 1273, 1993 April 27 (Box RT93_1273)
  - RT93 1274, 1993 April 27 (Box RT93_1274)
  - RT93 1275, 1993 April 27 (Box RT93_1275)
  - RT93 1276, 1993 April 27 (Box RT93_1276)
  - RT93 1277, 1993 April 27 (Box RT93_1277)
  - RT93 1278, 1993 April 28 (Box RT93_1278)
  - RT93 1279, 1993 April 28 (Box RT93_1279)
  - RT93 1280, 1995 March 20 (Box RT93_1280)
  - RT93 1281, 1993 April 22 (Box RT93_1281)
  - RT93 1282, 1993 April 22 (Box RT93_1282)
  - RT93 1283, 1993 April 22 (Box RT93_1283)
  - RT93 1284, 1993 April 22 (Box RT93_1284)
  - RT93 1285, 1993 April 28 (Box RT93_1285)
  - RT93 1286, 1993 April 28 (Box RT93_1286)
  - RT93 1287, 1993 April 28 (Box RT93_1287)
  - RT93 1288, 1993 April 30 (Box RT93_1288)
  - RT93 1289, 1993 April 30 (Box RT93_1289)
  - RT93 1290, 1993 April 30 (Box RT93_1290)
  - RT93 1291, 1993 April 30 (Box RT93_1291)
  - RT93 1292, 1993 April 30 (Box RT93_1292)
  - RT93 1293, 1993 April 29 (Box RT93_1293)
  - RT93 1294, 1993 May 7 (Box RT93_1294)
  - RT93 1295, 1993 May 7 (Box RT93_1295)
  - RT93 1296, 1993 April 27 (Box RT93_1296)
  - RT93 1297, 1993 April 30 (Box RT93_1297)
  - RT93 1298, 1993 April 27 (Box RT93_1298)
  - RT93 1299, 1993 April 27 (Box RT93_1299)
  - RT93 1300, 1993 April 27 (Box RT93_1300)
  - RT93 1301, 1993 May 17 (Box RT93_1301)
  - RT93 1302, 1993 May 17 (Box RT93_1302)
  - RT93 1303, Undated (Box RT93_1303)
  - RT93 1304, 1993 May 17 (Box RT93_1304)
  - RT93 1305, 1993 May 7 (Box RT93_1305)
  - RT93 1306, 1993 May 17 (Box RT93_1306)
  - RT93 1307, 1993 May 17 (Box RT93_1307)
  - RT93 1308, 1993 May 18 (Box RT93_1308)
  - RT93 1309, 1993 May 18 (Box RT93_1309)
  - RT93 1310, 1993 May 18 (Box RT93_1310)
  - RT93 1311, 1993 May 18 (Box RT93_1311)
  - RT93 1312, 1993 May 10 (Box RT93_1312)
  - RT93 1313, 1993 May 24 (Box RT93_1313)
  - RT93 1314, 1993 May 10 (Box RT93_1314)
  - RT93 1315 [has VHS use copy], 1993 (Box RT93_1315)
  - RT93 1316, 1993 May 22 (Box RT93_1316)
  - RT93 1317, 1993 May 19 (Box RT93_1317)
  - RT93 1318, 1993 May 19 (Box RT93_1318)
  - RT93 1320, 1993 May 19 (Box RT93_1320)
  - RT93 1321, 1993 May 25 (Box RT93_1321)
  - RT93 1322, 1993 May 4 (Box RT93_1322)
  - RT93 1323, 1993 May 4 (Box RT93_1323)
  - RT93 1324, 1993 May 4 (Box RT93_1324)
  - RT93 1325, 1993 April 23 (Box RT93_1325)
  - RT93 1326, 1993 April 23 (Box RT93_1326)
  - RT93 1327, 1993 May 22 (Box RT93_1327)
  - RT93 1328, 1993 May 22 (Box RT93_1328)
  - RT93 1329, 1993 May 20 (Box RT93_1329)
  - RT93 1330, 1993 May 20 (Box RT93_1330)
  - RT93 1331, 1993 May 29 (Box RT93_1331)
  - RT93 1332, 1993 May 29 (Box RT93_1332)
  - RT93 1333, 1993 May 29 (Box RT93_1333)
  - RT93 1334, 1993 May 29 (Box RT93_1334)
  - RT93 1335, 1993 April 5 (Box RT93_1335)
  - RT93 1336, 1993 April 5 (Box RT93_1336)
  - RT93 1337, 1993 June 1 (Box RT93_1337)
  - RT93 1338, 1993 June 1 (Box RT93_1338)
  - RT93 1339, 1993 June 1 (Box RT93_1339)
  - RT93 1340, 1993 March 3 (Box RT93_1340)
  - RT93 1341, 1993 May 28 (Box RT93_1341)
  - RT93 1342, 1993 May 26 (Box RT93_1342)
  - RT93 1343, 1993 May 1 (Box RT93_1343)
  - RT93 1344, 1993 May 1 (Box RT93_1344)
  - RT93 1345, 1993 May 1 (Box RT93_1345)
  - RT93 1346, 1993 May 26 (Box RT93_1346)
  - RT93 1347, 1993 May 1 (Box RT93_1347)
  - RT93 1348, 1993 June 7 (Box RT93_1348)
  - RT93 1349, 1993 June 7 (Box RT93_1349)
  - RT93 1351, Undated (Box RT93_1351)
  - RT93 1352, Undated (Box RT93_1352)
  - RT93 1353, 1993 May 27 (Box RT93_1353)
  - RT93 1354, 1993 May 27 (Box RT93_1354)
  - RT93 1355, 1993 June 9 (Box RT93_1355)
  - RT93 1356, 1993 June 9 (Box RT93_1356)
  - RT93 1357, 1993 June 11 (Box RT93_1357)
  - RT93 1358, 1993 June 11 (Box RT93_1358)
  - RT93 1359, 1993 May 29 (Box RT93_1359)
  - RT93 1360, Undated (Box RT93_1360)
  - RT93 1361, Undated (Box RT93_1361)
  - RT93 1362, Undated (Box RT93_1362)
  - RT93 1363, 1993 May 24 (Box RT93_1363)
  - RT93 1364, 1993 May 24 (Box RT93_1364)
  - RT93 1365, 1993 May 24 (Box RT93_1365)
  - RT93 1366, 1993 May 24 (Box RT93_1366)
  - RT93 1367, 1993 May 24 (Box RT93_1367)
  - RT93 1368, Undated (Box RT93_1368)
  - RT93 1369, 1993 May 24 (Box RT93_1369)
  - RT93 1370, 1993 April 5 (Box RT93_1370)
  - RT93 1371, 1994 April 6 (Box RT93_1371)
  - RT93 1372, 1993 June 11 (Box RT93_1372)
  - RT93 1373, 1993 May 27 (Box RT93_1373)
  - RT93 1374, 1993 April 8 (Box RT93_1374)
  - RT93 1375, 1993 April 8 (Box RT93_1375)
  - RT93 1378, Undated (Box RT93_1378)
  - RT93 1379, Undated (Box RT93_1379)
  - RT93 1380, Undated (Box RT93_1380)
  - RT93 1381, Undated (Box RT93_1381)
  - RT93 1382, Undated (Box RT93_1382)
  - RT93 1383, 1993 June 17 (Box RT93_1383)
  - RT93 1384, 1993 June 17 (Box RT93_1384)
  - RT93 1385, Undated (Box RT93_1385)
  - RT93 1386, 1993 June 17 (Box RT93_1386)
  - RT93 1387, Undated (Box RT93_1387)
  - RT93 1388, 1993 June 18 (Box RT93_1388)
  - RT93 1389, 1993 June 18 (Box RT93_1389)
  - RT93 1390, 1993 June 18 (Box RT93_1390)
  - RT93 1391, 1993 June 18 (Box RT93_1391)
  - RT93 1392, 1993 June 18 (Box RT93_1392)
  - RT93 1393, 1993 June 18 (Box RT93_1393)
  - RT93 1394, 1993 June 19 (Box RT93_1394)
  - RT93 1395, 1993 June 19 (Box RT93_1395)
  - RT93 1396, 1993 June 19 (Box RT93_1396)
  - RT93 1397, 1993 June 19 (Box RT93_1397)
  - RT93 1398, 1993 June 19 (Box RT93_1398)
  - RT93 1399, 1993 June 19 (Box RT93_1399)
  - RT93 1400, 1993 June 19 (Box RT93_1400)
  - RT93 1401, 1993 June 19 (Box RT93_1401)
  - RT93 1402, 1993 June 20 (Box RT93_1402)
  - RT93 1406, Undated (Box Rt93_1406)
  - RT93 1407, Undated (Box RT93_1407)
  - RT93 1408, Undated (Box RT93_1408)
  - RT93 1409, Undated (Box RT93_1409)
  - RT93 1411, Undated (Box RT93_1411)
  - RT93 1415, 1993 May 27 (Box RT93_1415)
  - RT93 1416, 1993 May 27 (Box RT93_1416)
  - RT93 1417, 1993 June 20 (Box RT93_1417)
  - RT93 1418, Undated (Box RT93_1418)
  - RT93 1419, 1993 May 24 (Box RT93_1419)
  - RT93 1420, 1993 May 24 (Box RT93_1420)
  - RT93 1421, 1993 May 24 (Box RT93_1421)
  - RT93 1422, 1993 May 24 (Box RT93_1422)
  - RT93 1423, 1993 May 24 (Box RT93_1423)
  - RT93 1424, 1993 May 24 (Box RT93_1424)
  - RT93 1425, 1993 May 24 (Box RT93_1425)
  - RT93 1426, 1993 May 24 (Box RT93_1426)
  - RT93 1427, 1993 June 20 (Box RT93_1427)
  - RT93 1428, Undated (Box RT93_1428)
  - RT93 1429, 1993 June 21 (Box RT93_1429)
  - RT93 1430, 1993 April 8 (Box RT93_1430)
  - RT93 1431, 1993 June 14 (Box RT93_1431)
  - RT93 1432, Undated (Box RT93_1432)
  - RT93 1433, Undated (Box RT93_1433)
  - RT94 1029, 1994 February 3 (Box RT94_1029)
  - RT94 1030, 1994 January 1 (Box RT94_1030)
  - RT94 1036, 1994 February 10 (Box RT94_1036)
  - RT94 1037, 1994 February 10 (Box RT94_1037)
  - RT94 1039, Undated (Box RT94_1039)
  - RT94 1040, Undated (Box RT94_1040)
  - RT94 1044, Undated (Box RT94_1044)
  - RT94 1045, Undated (Box RT94_1045)
  - RT94 1046, Undated (Box RT94_1046)
  - RT94 1047, 1994 March 9 (Box RT94_1047)
  - RT94 1048, 1994 March 2 (Box RT94_1048)
  - RT94 1049, 1994 March 2 (Box RT94_1049)
  - RT94 1050, 1994 March 2 (Box RT94_1050)
  - RT94 1051, 1994 March 2 (Box RT94_1051)
  - RT94 1052, 1994 March 3 (Box RT94_1052)
  - RT94 1053, 1994 March 3 (Box RT94_1053)
  - RT94 1054, 1994 March 4 (Box RT94_1054)
  - RT94 1055, 1994 March 4 (Box RT94_1055)
  - RT94 1056, 1994 March 4 (Box RT94_1056)
  - RT94 1057, 1994 March 4 (Box RT94_1057)
  - RT94 1058, 1994 March 4 (Box RT94_1058)
  - RT94 1059, 1994 March 5 (Box RT94_1059)
  - RT94 1060, 1004 March 6 (Box RT94_1060)
  - RT94 1061, 1994 March 7 (Box RT94_1061)
  - RT94 1062, 1004 March 8 (Box RT94_1062)
  - RT94 1063, 1994 March 8 (Box RT94_1063)
  - RT94 1064, 1994 March 8 (Box RT94_1064)
  - RT94 1065, 1994 March 10 (Box RT94_1065)
  - RT94 1066, 1994 March 1 (Box RT94_1066)
  - RT94 1067, 1994 March 1 (Box RT94_1067)
  - RT94 1068, 1994 March 1 (Box RT94_1068)
  - RT94 1069, 1994 March 1 (Box RT94_1069)
  - RT94 1070, 1994 March 14 (Box RT94_1070)
  - RT94 1071, 1994 March 14 (Box RT94_1071)
  - RT94 1072, 1994 March 15 (Box RT94_1072)
  - RT94 1073, 1994 March 15 (Box RT94_1073)
  - RT94 1074, 1994 March 15 (Box RT94_1074)
  - RT94 1075, Undated (Box RT94_1075)
  - RT94 1076, 1994 March 14 (Box RT94_1076)
  - RT94 1077, 1994 March 16 (Box RT94_1077)
  - RT94 1078, 1994 March 16 (Box RT94_1078)